tridoshawellness.com 2014-11-22

# Privacy Policy

**Privacy Policy for** Tridoshawellness.com

We respect your privacy at Tridoshawellness.com and all of our related sites. We do not distribute your personal information to any third parties. This includes not only your email address but any personal information you input during your use of the site. Here is information on what types of personal information we receive and collect when you visit the site, and how we safeguard your information.

1\. INTRODUCTION

1.1. PURPOSE OF POLICY. Tridoshawellness.com (“us,” “we,” or “Company”) is committed to respecting the privacy rights of its customers, visitors, and other users of the Company Website (the “Site”). We created this Website Privacy Policy (this “Policy”) to give you confidence as you visit and use the Site, and to demonstrate our commitment to fair information practices and the protection of privacy. This Policy is only applicable to the Site, and not to any other websites that you may be able to access from the Site, each of which may have data collection and use practices and policies that differ materially from this Policy.

2\. INFORMATION COLLECTION PRACTICES

2.1. WHAT BASIC INFORMATION DOES THE COMPANY COLLECT?

In operating the Site, Company may include newsletters, online commenting areas, and other online forms that ask users to provide their names, e-mail addresses, and other contact information.

2.2. WHAT ADDITIONAL INFORMATION DOES COMPANY COLLECT?

(a) AUTOMATIC COLLECTION. Our servers automatically recognize visitors’ domain names and IP addresses (the number assigned to computers on the Internet). No personal information about you is revealed in this process. The Site may also gather anonymous “traffic data” that does not personally identify you, but that may be helpful for marketing purposes or for improving the services we offer.

(b) COOKIES. From time to time, we may use the standard “cookies” feature of major browser applications that allows us to store a small piece of data on your computer about your visit to our Web site. Cookies help us learn which areas of our site are useful and which areas need improvement. You can choose whether to accept cookies by changing the settings on your browser. However, if you choose to disable this function, your experience at our Web site may be diminished and some features may not work as they were intended.

3\. USE AND SHARING OF INFORMATION

3.1. WHAT DOES COMPANY DO WITH COLLECTED INFORMATION?

(a) PERSONAL INFORMATION. We will not share your personal information with any third parties without your consent, except as necessary to provide you with the services offered by us or to comply with the law. We will use your information as a greater collection of data related to the site in traffic discussions in articles posted on the blog. No individual users visit, whether you or another visitor, are discussed. The aggregate data is used for education purposes only and no reader of the article will be able to identify you.

(b) ANONYMOUS INFORMATION. We use anonymous information to analyze our Site traffic. In addition, we may use anonymous IP addresses to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our site, or to display the content according to your preferences. Traffic and transaction information may also be shared with business partners and advertisers on an aggregate and anonymous basis.

(c) USE OF COOKIES. We may use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests or for other purposes. Promotions or advertisements displayed on our site may contain cookies. We do not have access to or control over information collected by outside advertisers on our site.

(d) DISCLOSURE OF PERSONAL INFORMATION. We may disclose personal information if required to do so by law or in the good-faith belief that such action is necessary to (1) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on Company or its parent company, subsidiaries or affiliates, (2) protect and defend the rights or property of Company or the users of the Site, or (3) act under exigent circumstances to protect the safety of the public or users of the Site.

(e) SALE OF INFORMATION. In order to accommodate changes in our business, we may sell or buy portions of our company or other companies or assets, including the information collected through this Web site. If Company or substantially all of its assets are acquired, customer information will be one of the assets transferred to the acquirer.

(f) ACCESS TO INFORMATION. Unfortunately, we do not maintain any procedures for you to review or request changes to the information that we collect about you, except that you may request that we remove all information about you from our database by contacting us in accordance with Section 6.1 below.

4\. SECURITY

The Site has security measures in place to prevent the loss, misuse, and alteration of the information that we obtain from you, but we make no assurances about our ability to prevent any such loss, misuse, to you or to any third party arising out of any such loss, misuse, or alteration.

5\. WEBSITE AREAS BEYOND COMPANY’S CONTROL

5.1. PUBLIC COMMENTS

The Site may include interactive sections such as commenting areas where visitors to the site can post comments. Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.

5.2. THIRD PARTY WEBSITES

The Site contains links to other websites. If you choose to visit other websites, we have no control over the privacy practices or content of those other websites, and it is your responsibility to review the privacy policies at those websites to confirm that you understand and agree with their policies.

6\. CONTACT INFORMATION AND POLICY UPDATES

6.1. CONTACTING US

If you have any questions about this Policy, our practices related to this Site, or if you would like to have us remove your information from our database please feel contact us at the following:

Tridosha Wellness Products, LLC,

407 Orange Street

Oakland, CA 94610

(510) 931-5700

support”at”tridoshawellness.com

6.2. UPDATES AND CHANGES

We reserve the right, at any time, to add to, change, update, or modify this Policy, simply by posting such change, update, or modification on the Site and without any other notice to you. Any such change, update, or modification will be effective immediately upon posting on the Site. It is your responsibility to review this Policy from time to time to ensure that you continue to agree with all of its terms.

Affiliate Disclaimer

Hi. Manu Kalia here. I’ve always believed in transparency on the web and so I am disclosing that I’ve included certain products and links to those products on this site that I will earn an affiliate commission for any purchases you make. My goal with the blog is to help educate you on natural health and fitness solutions, but please understand I am doing this as a for-profit business.

You should assume that any links leading you to products or services are affiliate links that I will receive compensation from just to be safe. Having said that, there are millions of products and services on the web that relate to health and fitness. I only promote those products or services that I have investigated and truly feel deliver value to you.

Please note that I have not been given any free products, services or anything else by these companies in exchange for mentioning them on the site. The only consideration is in the form of affiliate commissions.

If you have any questions regarding the above, please do not hesitate to contact me by using the contact page.

Cheers!

Manu Kalia
